==AVANT==
==OP==
===MAIN===
===INSERT===
That make you felel alive?
============
===INSERT===
===ED===
===NEXT===
死吧！露娜
ねぇ今 どうして僕ら生まれたの
ねぇほら どうして僕ら出会ったの
わからなくて恐いから つないだこの手を
今君に 強く握り返して欲しいんだ
傷付ける現実から 逃れようとして
幻みたいな存在に 全てを期待した
押し寄せる感情や 迷わせる葛藤も
抱きながら前に 前に進みたいんだ
ひび割れた丘 錆びた空の下 生きる僕らまるで青い花
寄り添い泡沫の夢を見る それでもまだ枯れたくはない
ねぇ今 どうして僕ら生まれたの
ねぇほら どうして僕ら出会ったの
わからなくて恐いから つないだこの手を
今君に 強く握り返して欲しいんだ
走这边 请快一点！
希望的赞歌
请退后
为何要对我们下手
为什么？为了活下去啊
从今天起你们就要成为我们身体的一部分而活下去
感谢我们吧
而且 在毁灭之中 希望是无法存在下去的
保护希望是我们的工作
过来吧
毁灭吧
就只剩下你一个
希望陨落的时刻到了
你要干什么！
I wanna be a star
That Never stop
Oh...shining down on you
I wanna be a moon
Like a gentle wind
Oh...softly touch your face
Feel my breath When you close your eyes at night
It's alright You are not the only one
I will be the waves carrying your boat
I'll find your day...
住口！
What do you wanna be
不要唱了！
if there is a choice?
杀了你！
Do you have a dream
这是...
嗯 卡辛干的吧
虽然不知道发生了什么事
卡辛
很动听的歌声呢
为什么？
为什么 你会在那种情况下歌唱？
你 又为何要杀戮？
不杀他们的话...
为了生命 去杀戮吗
我是为了歌唱而生的
所以歌唱
你是为了杀戮而生的吗
好像玩笑开得有点过分了呢
非常感谢你救了我
你真是很特别
拥有这般力量 看起来却因为这般力量而困惑
这般力量 有意义吗
这个世界上 没有意义的东西
是不存在的
能否找出意义 就要看自己
只要能找到那个意义 人就可以毫不犹豫地前进
我为了生存而歌唱
你总有一天 会找到战斗的意义
我一直以某个地方为目标 不断地旅行
某个地方？
从很久前开始 我就一直以那里为目标
那个地方还在吗
不知道
毁灭的速度比我预想的要快
蔓延到世界的每个角落
不过我相信
因为无论是谁都需要希望
你 真是不可思议
彼此彼此吧
你接下来要怎么办？
我可以跟着你吗
佳妮诗 她的歌声可以使人忘却毁灭的恐怖
歌姬 佳妮诗
播撒破坏与绝望的男人
与能让人在片刻间忘却毁灭的恐怖的女人
简直就像矛与盾一样
又不是你的错 为何这般心事重重
错的是毁灭
真的是这样吗
我...
为何这般胆怯
我... 在胆怯？
不是吗
不知道
他们的死亡 毁灭的出现 都是我...
没事的
不是你的错
死吧
没事吧
这是...
这么说... 你... 是卡辛
是这样啊 怪不得这么强
那么 那位就是佳妮诗吧
你为什么会知道？
你们两个不久就会到达巴萨的事情 在这一带已经传开了
为了追寻希望 好像有不少猎物聚集在那里
为了成为我们的饲饵
小心一点吧 你会第一个被盯上
因为那种让人讨厌的歌声
你！
请带我去 拜托了
人们在等着我 所以 拜托了！
是那个时候的歌声
嗯 是吗
卡辛 现在在做什么啊
用他自己的方式在苦恼挣扎吧
一边苦恼挣扎 一边战斗
我们也要去看看吗
巴萨
从很久以前起就是我的目标
巴萨音乐厅
很久以前在这里听过某个人的歌
我的心灵为之震颤
那歌声飘渺而有力
那歌声仿佛附着在我身上
于是我决定了 总有一天要在这里唱自己的歌
从那以后 我就坚持歌唱
祈祷着 我的歌声能够传达到人们的心里 直到现在
真是讽刺啊
世界的毁灭蔓延的越是广泛
我的歌声越是能传达到人们的内心
现在毁灭降临到我的身上
过去为了让大家听到我的歌声 我一直歌唱到现在
不过
今天我要为自己的歌声能够传达到你的心里而歌唱
太好了 您没事 不枉我一直这里等候
欧吉 快点 快点
欧吉
You listen to my voice Listen to my heart
Now I see it clearly
You listen to your voice Listen to your heart
Do your even smile?
There is nothing you can't do
Only you can do is to make youself happy
You listen to your voice Listen to your heart
Make yourself alive
We are free
Like water flows
We are one as we feel the love
How long will it take to find a way out?
But she never lost the way and made herself to home
So we hold each other's hand as we walk along the way
No matter fears and tears to fall
We find a way of home...
We are free Like water flows
We are one as we feel the love
How long will they take to find a way out
But she never lost the way and made herself to home
So we hold each other's hand
as we walk along the way
No matter fears and tears to fall
We find the way of home...
How long will they take to find a way out
But she never lost the way and made herself to home
So we hold each other's hand as we walk along the way
No matter fears and tears to fall
We find a way of home...
You listen to my voice Listen to my heart
Now I see it clearly
You listen to your voice Listen to your heart
Do you even smile?
あふれる涙のその理由を
問うのはもうやめましょう
夜明けの蒼が満ちたなら
明日へ漕ぎ出しましょう
優しいだけじゃ生きられずに誰かを傷つけて
裸のままじゃ生きられずに誰かを抱きしめる
Nobody knows the reason why 苦しくなるなら
どうして愛を知るの
Nobody knows the place to go 終わりがあるから
こんなに求めあうの
有一位被遗忘的少女
怀着忠贞不变的思念
下集 在毁灭的山谷中绽放的鲜花